https://www.seductionscience.com/trms/privacy-policy/

0
No videos yet!Click on "Watch later" to put videos here
HomeLatestMy CoursesCoachingMoreContactAbout JesseForumsPrivacy PolicyInformation Collection & UseSEDUCTION SCIENCE is the sole owner of the information collected on SEDUCTION SCIENCE.COM. SEDUCTION SCIENCE collects personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our Web site.OrdersIf you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date).We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.When placing an order, we record your internet protocol (IP) address for security purposes in the case of credit card fraud.You may opt to make credit card payments through PayPal.com. This information is collected solely for PayPal to securely process the order.No information sold or distributed to third parties.Communications from the SiteNewslettersIf you wish to subscribe to our newsletter, we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe.If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by contacting us here.Your email address will be used solely for sending emails, exclusively from this source. Neither your email address nor your identity will be sold, leased, rented or disclosed to individuals or organisations outside Seduction Science.Customer ServiceBased upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your orders. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes.Information Sharing and DisclosureAggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)We DO NOT share aggregated demographic information about our user base with Advertisers or Third Parties.Personally identifiable informationWe DO NOT rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people, nonaffiliated companies, advertisers, or Third Parties.Legal DisclaimerWe reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web siteLog FilesAs is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information, nor are IP addresses are not tied to personally identifiable information.We use in-house custom tracking software that uses log files to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate, specifically referring pages to determine which sites traffic is coming from.CookiesA cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We DO NOT link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.We DO NOT use session ID cookies but we do use persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file.We set a persistent cookie to track which ads users have clicked on to reach the site. Persistent cookies also enable us to track which of our affiliate partners have brought us traffic and orders.If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, and your ability to use our site will not be compromised.SEDUCTION SCIENCE.COM does not have Third Parties nor Third Parties that use cookies on this site. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by SEDUCTION SCIENCE.COM only.Links to Other SitesThis Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by SEDUCTION SCIENCE. Please be aware that we, SEDUCTION SCIENCE are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information.This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site.Bulletin BoardsIf you use a bulletin board on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.Although the administrators and moderators of bulletin boards will attempt to keep all objectionable messages off the forum, it is impossible for us to review all messages. All messages express the views of the author, and neither SEDUCTION SCIENCE.COM, nor Jelsoft Enterprises Ltd. (developers of vBulletin) will be held responsible for the content of any message.By agreeing to these rules, you warrant that you will not post any messages that are obscene, vulgar, sexually-orientated, hateful, threatening, or otherwise violative of any laws.We reserve the right to remove, edit, move or close any thread for any reason.SecurityThe security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information such as a credit card number on our order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.Business TransitionsIn the event SEDUCTION SCIENCE goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email and a prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.Changes in this Privacy StatementIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.
